35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Tibet, 1949; 2 (Box 1583)
    - [Tibetan monks walking down stairs], 2
    - [Tibetan street performers], 3
    - [Tibetan people wearing red hats and robes], 4
    - [Tibetan women in a garden in Tibet], 5
    - [Snowcapped mountains in Tibet], 6
    - [Tibetan people on the bank of river in Tibet], 7
    - [Close-up of flowers growing in a field in Tibet], 8
    - [Tibetan artwork], 9
    - [Village in Tibet], 10
    - [Tibetan people walking on dirt raod, village in distance], 11
    - [Tibetan man rowing a boat on river running by the Potala Palace], 12
    - [Tibetan monks gathered], 13
    - [Tibetan soldiers riding horses on dirt road], 14
    - [Roof to Tibetan building], 15
    - [Tibetan man with donkeys(?)], 16
    - [Tibetan monks], 17
    - [People hiking up hillside in Tibet], 18
    - [Tibetan people standing outside of wall in Tibet], 19
    - [Person holding red object, in Tibet], 20
  - Tibet, 1949; 3 (Box 1583)
    - [Donkey walking on dirt road], 1
    - [Tibetan people putting on performance on the streets in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan monks standing on stairs in Tibet], 3
    - [Tibetan people riding donkeys on mountainside], 4
    - [Tibetan people crossing bridge on donkeys], 5
    - [Dai Lama in Tibet], 6
    - [Tibetan statue of a woman], 7
    - [Little Tibetan girl], 8
    - [Group of monks and Lowell Thomas, Jr. in Tibet], 9
    - [Crowd of monks in street in Tibet], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. talking to Tibetan people beside the river in Tibet], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. talking to a Tibetan woman dressed in a bright dress in Tibet], 12
    - [Tibetan man working with a type of paste in Tibet], 13
    - [Tibetan sheep herdsman in Tibet], 14
    - [Flowers growing in Tibet], 15
    - [Monk looking at Tibetan artwork], 16
  - Tibet, 1949; 4 (Box 1583)
    - [Camp set up, snowcapped mountain in the distance in Tibet], 1
    - [Close-up of Tibetan woman dressed in a bright dress in Tibet], 2
    - [Building in ruins, Tibet], 3
    - [View of town in Tibet], 4
    - [Artwork in Tibet], 5
    - [Village street in Tibet], 6
    - [Large palace in Tibet], 7
    - [(Dark photo) Tibetan people riding in a carriage in Tibet], 8
    - [Two Tibetan men standing at the end of a hill in Tibet], 9
  - Tibet, 1949; 5 (Box 1583)
    - [Group of Tibetan children in Tibet], 1
    - [Two men sitting eating fruit in front of ocean in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan man standing on the top of a stone wall], 3
    - [Tibetan person raising a hammer above a rock in Tibet], 4
    - [Two men standing in front of ocean in Tibet], 5
    - [View of hill in Tibet], 6
    - [Ruined building in Tibet], 7
    - [Tibetan herdsman with sheep in Tibet], 8
    - [View of hills and ocean in Tibet], 9
  - Tibet, 1949; 6 (Box 1583)
    - [View of river running between hills in Tibet], 1
    - [Tibetan woman working by a little creek in Tibet], 2
    - [Docked ship in Tibet], 3
    - [Tibetan monks gathered together], 4
    - [Tibetan woman by riverside, brandishing a stick], 5
    - [Ruined building in Tibet], 6
    - [View of mountains in Tibet], 7
    - [Tibetan women working by a creek], 8
    - [Tibetan people playing instruments near a horse-drawn carriage on a road in Tibet], 9
  - Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)], circa 1954, circa 1975; 7 (Box 1583)
    - [Beginning of Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)], 1
    - [Beginning of Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)]], 2
    - [Beginning of Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)]], 3
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Newspaper article from the Pawling Chronicle and golf scorecards], 4
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golfing rules for Hammersley Hill Golf Club], 5
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: House, Lowell Thomas sitting in a golf cart with his dog], 6
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 7
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Man taking a picture of Lowell Thomas putting], 9
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas in a golf cart with Frances Ryan Thomas ], 10
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 11
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 12
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Aerial view of a golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: View of a pond (part of golf course)], 14
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course], 15
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Paved road], 16
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course], 18
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course and lake], 19
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course], 20
  - Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)], circa 1954, circa 1975; 8 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas in golf cart with three people standing by, smiling], 1
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Two ladies with Lowell Thomas on golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Two women at picnic table, Lowell Thomas standing nearby], 3
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas and young girl], 4
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas talking with two women], 5
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas and a woman on golf course by a lake], 6
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Two women and Lowell Thomas on golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas talking with a woman by a lake on golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas with a woman on golf course by a lake], 9
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas talking to a woman by a lake on golf course], 10
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas flipping through a book with a woman on the golf course near a lake], 11
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas sitting on a picnic table talking with a woman on the golf course], 12
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a woman on the golf course ], 13
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas posing for a picture with a woman on the golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas posing for a picture with a woman on the golf course], 15
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Woman walking on golf course], 16
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas posing for a picture with a woman on the golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Dog on a leash on the golf course ], 18
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas with a woman looking through a book], 19
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Man with a dog on a leash on a golf cart], 20
  - Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)], circa 1954, circa 1975; 9 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Aerial view of a large estate], 1
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Road running past a house], 2
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Driveway leading up to house in the distance], 3
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Mansion], 4
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Sideview of house], 5
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: View of bushes and flowers], 6
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: A tree that's leaves turned golden/yellow for autumn], 7
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Car parked in driveway], 8
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas (in wheelchair) and another man in front of large portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas when she was younger], 9
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas (in wheelchair) and another man in front of large portrait of Frances Ryan Thomas when she was younger], 10
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas with two other men inside house with golf clubs], 11
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Pool], 12
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Pool], 13
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Indoor pool], 14
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Indoor pool], 15
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 16
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 17
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 18
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 19
  - Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)], circa 1954, circa 1975; 10 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 1
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 2
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 3
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 4
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 5
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 6
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 7
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 8
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 9
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 10
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 11
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 12
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Mansion covered with snow], 13
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Mansion covered with snow], 14
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Side of mansion covered with snow], 15
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 16
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 17
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 18
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 19
  - Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)], circa 1954, circa 1975; 11 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter], 1
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter, people on skiis], 2
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter, three people on course], 3
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the winter, three people on course], 4
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during winter, two people on skiis], 5
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during winter, man on skiis], 6
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Estate during the fall], 7
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: View of golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Road running by golf course], 9
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the fall], 10
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the fall], 11
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Golf course during the fall], 12
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: (Black and white photo) Lowell Thomas and two other men in golf cart], 13
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas talking with another man inside house], 14
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Letter to Lowell Thomas from Richard Nixon about Nixon's membership to the Hammersley Hill Club, photo next to it of man (Nixon?) swinging golf club], 15
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas standing with four other men outside], 16
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas talking with two other men], 17
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas in a golf cart with another man], 18
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas holding an oversized golfclub next to another man in front of golf cart], 19
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Group photo of men on golf course, Lowell Thomas is in the front row to the left], 20
  - Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate (circa 1975); golf (circa 1954)] [Items 1-8] Carousel number 2 [Items 9-20], circa 1954, circa 1975; 12 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Man and two little boys on golf cart], 1
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas and three other men by golf cart], 2
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas with three other men on golf cart], 3
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas and group of men with golf clubs], 4
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas linking arms with one man, another man standing to the left], 5
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas standing with three other men with golf clubs], 6
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas seated in golf cart with another man], 7
    - [Carousel number 1 [Hammersley Hill Estate]: Lowell Thomas holding and oversized golf club with another man], 8
    - Beginning of Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing], 9
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man and woman standing together with golf clubs], 10
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Two men sitting in golf cart with clubs], 11
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Three men and a golf cart], 12
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Men driving golf carts], 13
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Two men in a golf cart], 14
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Two men in a golf cart], 15
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man sitting in a golf cart], 16
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas and two other men by a golf cart], 17
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Two men sitting in golf cart, Lowell Thomas standing next to them], 18
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas talking to a man in a golf cart], 19
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man sitting in golf cart], 20
  - Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing], circa 1970s; 13 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas and man in golf cart], 1
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas and man in golf cart], 2
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man standing outside of house], 3
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man standing outside of house], 4
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Two men standing together at golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Woman standing outside of house, smiling], 6
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man getting ready to putt with golf club], 7
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People having a picnic, Lowell Thomas standing in the back], 8
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People having a picnic, Lowell Thomas standing], 9
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Men sitting in lawn chairs], 10
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People having a picnic, Lowell Thomas standing], 11
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man sitting in golf cart with dog], 12
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man sitting in golf cart with dog], 13
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Golf carts lined up on course], 14
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Wall?], 15
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: View of a resort, mountains in the background], 16
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man standing on golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas and another man sitting in golf cart], 18
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Food laid out on outdoor table], 19
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas and another man sitting in a golf cart], 20
  - Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing], circa 1970s; 14 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]:Lowell Thomas and man sitting in golf cart], 1
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man leaning against stone wall, holding a cat], 2
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Woman holding her pet cat], 3
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]:Man holding pet cat], 4
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Woman standing by door to house], 5
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas sitting at edge of desk], 6
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas sitting at edge of desk], 7
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas sitting at edge of desk], 8
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas sitting at edge of desk], 9
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Woman sitting on porch chair], 10
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Woman sitting on porch chair], 11
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]:Lowell Thomas standing in front of giraffe exhibit], 12
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Giraffe], 13
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Giraffe exhibit], 14
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Giraffe exhibit], 15
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Wildabeast], 16
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Wildabeast], 17
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Campus map for Colorado Women's College], 18
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Building (religious building?)], 19
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Building (religious building?)], 20
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Campus building], 21
  - Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing], circa 1970s; 15 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Woman standing in front of of "Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun"], 1